divshot.com 2014-06-25

# Divshot - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Divshot we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can't stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our [support team](mailto:support@divshot.com).

Divshot Inc. ( **Divshot** ) operates divshot.com. It is Divshot's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

##### Basically,

This is what we think about your privacy.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Divshot collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Divshot’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Divshot’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Divshot may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Divshot also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Divshot does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

##### Basically,

We collect anonymous information to make Divshot better.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Divshot’s websites choose to interact with Divshot in ways that require Divshot to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Divshot gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at [Divshot.com](http://www.divshot.com/) to provide a username and email address. Divshot collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Divshot. Divshot does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

##### Basically,

We ask really nicely for your non-anonymous information, but you don't have to give it to us. We will never sell your information.

### Aggregated Statistics

Divshot may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Divshot may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Divshot does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

##### Basically,

Website statistics are interesting.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Divshot discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Divshot’s behalf or to provide services available at Divshot’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Divshot’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Divshot will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Divshot discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Divshot believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Divshot, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Divshot website and have supplied your email address, Divshot may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Divshot and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Divshot takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

##### Basically,

Your secret is safe with us.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Divshot uses cookies to help Divshot identify and track visitors, their usage of Divshot website, and their website access preferences. Divshot visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Divshot’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Divshot’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

##### Basically,

We like you, have a cookie, home baked by our servers.

### Business Transfers

If Divshot, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Divshot goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Divshot may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

##### Basically,

Things can happen. We'll let you know if things do.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Divshot may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Divshot’s sole discretion. Divshot encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

##### Basically,

We can update this thing once in awhile.
